[
  {
    "question_no.": 1,
    "Question": "Introducing a man, a woman said, 'His mother is the only daughter of my mother-in-law.' How is the woman related to the man?",
    "Option1": "Mother",
    "Option2": "Aunt",
    "Option3": "Sister",
    "Option4": "Wife",
    "Answer": "Mother"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 2,
    "Question": "Pointing to a photograph, a man says, 'I have no brother or sister but that man's father is my father's son.' Who is in the photograph?",
    "Option1": "His son",
    "Option2": "His father",
    "Option3": "His uncle",
    "Option4": "His nephew",
    "Answer": "His son"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 3,
    "Question": "A is the father of C. D is the son of B. E is the brother of A. C is the sister of D. How is B related to E?",
    "Option1": "Mother",
    "Option2": "Sister-in-law",
    "Option3": "Daughter-in-law",
    "Option4": "Brother-in-law",
    "Answer": "Sister-in-law"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 4,
    "Question": "If 'A + B' means 'A is the father of B', 'A - B' means 'A is the wife of B', 'A x B' means 'A is the brother of B', and 'A / B' means 'A is the daughter of B', then how is P related to T in the expression 'P - Q + R x T'?",
    "Option1": "Mother",
    "Option2": "Sister",
    "Option3": "Wife",
    "Option4": "Sister-in-law",
    "Answer": "Mother"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 5,
    "Question": "Pointing to a lady, a man said, 'The son of her only brother is the brother of my wife.' How is the lady related to the man?",
    "Option1": "Mother",
    "Option2": "Grandmother",
    "Option3": "Sister of Father-in-law",
    "Option4": "Maternal Aunt",
    "Answer": "Sister of Father-in-law"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 6,
    "Question": "If 'P is the brother of Q', 'Q is the sister of R', 'R is the father of S', then how is P related to S?",
    "Option1": "Father",
    "Option2": "Uncle",
    "Option3": "Brother",
    "Option4": "Grandfather",
    "Answer": "Uncle"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 7,
    "Question": "A is B's sister. C is B's mother. D is C's father. E is D's mother. Then how is A related to D?",
    "Option1": "Grandfather",
    "Option2": "Grandmother",
    "Option3": "Daughter",
    "Option4": "Granddaughter",
    "Answer": "Granddaughter"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 8,
    "Question": "Looking at a portrait of a man, Harsh said, 'His mother is the wife of my father's son.' Brothers and sisters I have none. At whose portrait was Harsh looking?",
    "Option1": "His son",
    "Option2": "His nephew",
    "Option3": "His cousin",
    "Option4": "His uncle",
    "Answer": "His son"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 9,
    "Question": "A tells B, 'C is my father's nephew. D is A's aunt. C is D's son.' How is D related to B?",
    "Option1": "Sister",
    "Option2": "Mother",
    "Option3": "Aunt",
    "Option4": "Wife",
    "Answer": "Mother"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 10,
    "Question": "If P is the husband of Q, and R is the mother of S and Q, how is R related to P?",
    "Option1": "Mother",
    "Option2": "Sister",
    "Option3": "Mother-in-law",
    "Option4": "Aunt",
    "Answer": "Mother-in-law"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 11,
    "Question": "Pointing to a gentleman, Deepak said, 'His only brother is the father of my daughter's father.' How is the gentleman related to Deepak?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Uncle",
    "Option3": "Father",
    "Option4": "Brother-in-law",
    "Answer": "Uncle"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 12,
    "Question": "A is the son of B. C is the daughter of B. D is the mother of E. F is the son of A. E is the brother of F. How is B related to D?",
    "Option1": "Father-in-law",
    "Option2": "Mother-in-law",
    "Option3": "Husband",
    "Option4": "Wife",
    "Answer": "Father-in-law"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 13,
    "Question": "If 'A + B' means 'A is the mother of B', 'A - B' means 'A is the husband of B', 'A x B' means 'A is the son of B', and 'A / B' means 'A is the daughter of B', then what does 'P + Q - R' mean in terms of P's relation to R?",
    "Option1": "Mother-in-law",
    "Option2": "Grandmother",
    "Option3": "Mother",
    "Option4": "Aunt",
    "Answer": "Grandmother"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 14,
    "Question": "Kiran says, 'My mother is the only daughter of your mother.' Who is 'your' here?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Sister",
    "Option3": "Mother",
    "Option4": "Father",
    "Answer": "Brother"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 15,
    "Question": "Pointing to a man in a photograph, a woman said, 'He is the son of my mother's only daughter.' How is the man related to the woman?",
    "Option1": "Nephew",
    "Option2": "Son",
    "Option3": "Cousin",
    "Option4": "Brother",
    "Answer": "Son"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 16,
    "Question": "A and B are brothers. C and D are sisters. A's son is D's brother. How is B related to C?",
    "Option1": "Father",
    "Option2": "Brother",
    "Option3": "Uncle",
    "Option4": "Grandfather",
    "Answer": "Uncle"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 17,
    "Question": "If 'M x N' means 'M is the father of N', 'M + N' means 'M is the daughter of N', 'M - N' means 'M is the sister of N', then how is A related to C in 'A + B - C'?",
    "Option1": "Daughter",
    "Option2": "Niece",
    "Option3": "Aunt",
    "Option4": "Mother",
    "Answer": "Niece"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 18,
    "Question": "Pointing to a photo, a man tells his friend, 'She is the daughter of the only son of my father's wife.' How is the woman in the photo related to the man?",
    "Option1": "Mother",
    "Option2": "Daughter",
    "Option3": "Sister",
    "Option4": "Niece",
    "Answer": "Daughter"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 19,
    "Question": "A is the mother of B. B is the sister of C. C is the father of D. How is A related to D?",
    "Option1": "Mother",
    "Option2": "Grandmother",
    "Option3": "Aunt",
    "Option4": "Mother-in-law",
    "Answer": "Grandmother"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 20,
    "Question": "Introducing a girl, a boy said, 'She is the daughter of the only daughter of my maternal grandfather.' How is the girl related to the boy?",
    "Option1": "Sister",
    "Option2": "Cousin",
    "Option3": "Mother",
    "Option4": "Aunt",
    "Answer": "Sister"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 21,
    "Question": "If 'A @ B' means 'A is the daughter of B', 'A # B' means 'A is the husband of B', 'A * B' means 'A is the brother of B', then what does 'P @ Q # R * S' imply about P's relation to S?",
    "Option1": "Daughter-in-law",
    "Option2": "Niece",
    "Option3": "Sister",
    "Option4": "Daughter",
    "Answer": "Niece"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 22,
    "Question": "A is the son of P. Q is the daughter of A. R is the mother of Q. S is the brother of R. How is S related to A?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Uncle",
    "Option3": "Brother-in-law",
    "Option4": "Father",
    "Answer": "Brother-in-law"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 23,
    "Question": "Pointing to a man, a woman said, 'His mother is the only daughter of my mother.' How is the woman related to the man?",
    "Option1": "Mother",
    "Option2": "Aunt",
    "Option3": "Sister",
    "Option4": "Daughter",
    "Answer": "Mother"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 24,
    "Question": "If 'P & Q' means 'P is the father of Q', 'P % Q' means 'P is the daughter of Q', 'P $ Q' means 'P is the sister of Q', then how is M related to R in 'M % N & R'?",
    "Option1": "Daughter",
    "Option2": "Mother",
    "Option3": "Granddaughter",
    "Option4": "Grandmother",
    "Answer": "Granddaughter"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 25,
    "Question": "A is the brother of B. C is the sister of D. E is the mother of A. D is the son of E. How is B related to D?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Sister",
    "Option3": "Can't be determined",
    "Option4": "Father",
    "Answer": "Can't be determined"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 26,
    "Question": "Pointing to a man in a picture, Sanjeev said, 'His mother's only daughter is my mother.' How is Sanjeev related to the man?",
    "Option1": "Nephew",
    "Option2": "Brother",
    "Option3": "Son",
    "Option4": "Uncle",
    "Answer": "Nephew"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 27,
    "Question": "If 'A + B' means 'A is the mother of B', 'A - B' means 'A is the husband of B', 'A x B' means 'A is the son of B', then how is P related to R in 'P x Q + R'?",
    "Option1": "Son",
    "Option2": "Grandson",
    "Option3": "Father",
    "Option4": "Grandfather",
    "Answer": "Grandson"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 28,
    "Question": "A is the brother of B. B is the brother of C. D is the father of A. How is D related to C?",
    "Option1": "Father",
    "Option2": "Mother",
    "Option3": "Uncle",
    "Option4": "Brother",
    "Answer": "Father"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 29,
    "Question": "Introducing a woman, a man said, 'Her mother is the only daughter of my mother.' How is the man related to the woman?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Father",
    "Option3": "Uncle",
    "Option4": "Son",
    "Answer": "Brother"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 30,
    "Question": "Pointing to a woman in a photograph, a man says, 'She is the mother-in-law of the husband of my mother's only daughter.' How is the woman related to the man?",
    "Option1": "Mother",
    "Option2": "Grandmother",
    "Option3": "Aunt",
    "Option4": "Mother-in-law",
    "Answer": "Mother"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 31,
    "Question": "If 'P is the son of Q', 'Q is the sister of R', 'R is the mother of S', then how is P related to S?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Cousin",
    "Option3": "Nephew",
    "Option4": "Uncle",
    "Answer": "Cousin"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 32,
    "Question": "A and B are married couple. X and Y are brothers. X is the brother of A. How is Y related to B?",
    "Option1": "Brother-in-law",
    "Option2": "Brother",
    "Option3": "Son",
    "Option4": "Father",
    "Answer": "Brother-in-law"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 33,
    "Question": "If 'M @ N' means 'M is the son of N', 'M # N' means 'M is the wife of N', 'M % N' means 'M is the daughter of N', then how is P related to R in 'P % Q # R'?",
    "Option1": "Son",
    "Option2": "Daughter",
    "Option3": "Mother",
    "Option4": "Father",
    "Answer": "Father"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 34,
    "Question": "Pointing to a lady, a girl said, 'She is the daughter of the only sister of my father.' How is the lady related to the girl?",
    "Option1": "Mother",
    "Option2": "Aunt",
    "Option3": "Sister",
    "Option4": "Cousin",
    "Answer": "Cousin"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 35,
    "Question": "A is B's father. C is B's daughter. D is C's brother. E is A's sister. How is E related to D?",
    "Option1": "Mother",
    "Option2": "Aunt",
    "Option3": "Grandmother",
    "Option4": "Sister",
    "Answer": "Aunt"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 36,
    "Question": "Introducing a boy, a girl said, 'He is the son of the daughter of the father of my aunt.' How is the boy related to the girl?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Cousin",
    "Option3": "Uncle",
    "Option4": "Nephew",
    "Answer": "Cousin"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 37,
    "Question": "If 'A + B' means 'A is the father of B', 'A - B' means 'A is the wife of B', 'A x B' means 'A is the brother of B', how is M related to P in 'M + N - P'?",
    "Option1": "Father",
    "Option2": "Grandfather",
    "Option3": "Mother",
    "Option4": "Grandmother",
    "Answer": "Grandfather"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 38,
    "Question": "P and Q are brothers. R and S are sisters. P's son is S's brother. How is Q related to R?",
    "Option1": "Father",
    "Option2": "Uncle",
    "Option3": "Brother",
    "Option4": "Son",
    "Answer": "Uncle"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 39,
    "Question": "Pointing to a man, a woman said, 'His mother is the mother of my only son.' How is the woman related to the man?",
    "Option1": "Sister",
    "Option2": "Mother",
    "Option3": "Wife",
    "Option4": "Aunt",
    "Answer": "Sister"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 40,
    "Question": "A is B's mother. C is A's son. D is B's daughter. How is D related to C?",
    "Option1": "Sister",
    "Option2": "Cousin",
    "Option3": "Niece",
    "Option4": "Aunt",
    "Answer": "Sister"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 41,
    "Question": "Introducing a man, a woman said, 'His wife is the only daughter of my father.' How is the woman related to the man?",
    "Option1": "Mother",
    "Option2": "Sister",
    "Option3": "Wife",
    "Option4": "Daughter",
    "Answer": "Wife"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 42,
    "Question": "If 'P @ Q' means 'P is the sister of Q', 'P # Q' means 'P is the brother of Q', 'P $ Q' means 'P is the father of Q', then how is M related to S in 'M # N @ O $ S'?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Uncle",
    "Option3": "Father",
    "Option4": "Grandfather",
    "Answer": "Uncle"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 43,
    "Question": "A is the son of B. B is the father of C. C is the brother of D. How is D related to A?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Sister",
    "Option3": "Brother or Sister",
    "Option4": "Son",
    "Answer": "Brother or Sister"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 44,
    "Question": "Pointing to a boy, Meena said, 'He is the only son of my paternal grandfather's only daughter.' How is the boy related to Meena?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Cousin",
    "Option3": "Uncle",
    "Option4": "Nephew",
    "Answer": "Cousin"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 45,
    "Question": "X and Y are brothers. R is the father of X. S is the mother of T. X is the son of S. How is R related to T?",
    "Option1": "Father",
    "Option2": "Uncle",
    "Option3": "Father-in-law",
    "Option4": "Grandfather",
    "Answer": "Father"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 46,
    "Question": "If 'A + B' means 'A is the son of B', 'A - B' means 'A is the daughter of B', 'A x B' means 'A is the wife of B', then how is P related to R in 'P + Q x R'?",
    "Option1": "Son",
    "Option2": "Grandson",
    "Option3": "Father",
    "Option4": "Daughter-in-law",
    "Answer": "Son"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 47,
    "Question": "A is the husband of B. C is the mother of B. D is the mother of C. How is D related to A?",
    "Option1": "Mother",
    "Option2": "Grandmother",
    "Option3": "Mother-in-law",
    "Option4": "Grandmother-in-law",
    "Answer": "Grandmother-in-law"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 48,
    "Question": "Introducing a woman, a man said, 'Her husband's brother is my only brother.' How is the woman related to the man?",
    "Option1": "Sister",
    "Option2": "Sister-in-law",
    "Option3": "Mother",
    "Option4": "Aunt",
    "Answer": "Sister-in-law"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 49,
    "Question": "If 'M & N' means 'M is the brother of N', 'M % N' means 'M is the father of N', 'M $ N' means 'M is the wife of N', then how is P related to R in 'P & Q $ R'?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Brother-in-law",
    "Option3": "Uncle",
    "Option4": "Son",
    "Answer": "Brother-in-law"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 50,
    "Question": "A is the father of B. C is the daughter of A. D is the sister of B. E is the son of C. How is E related to D?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Nephew",
    "Option3": "Cousin",
    "Option4": "Uncle",
    "Answer": "Nephew"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 51,
    "Question": "Pointing to a man in a photo, a woman says, 'He is the son of the only daughter of my grandfather.' How is the man related to the woman?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Cousin",
    "Option3": "Son",
    "Option4": "Nephew",
    "Answer": "Brother"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 52,
    "Question": "If 'X + Y' means 'X is the mother of Y', 'X - Y' means 'X is the brother of Y', 'X * Y' means 'X is the father of Y', then how is A related to D in 'A + B * C - D'?",
    "Option1": "Grandmother",
    "Option2": "Mother",
    "Option3": "Aunt",
    "Option4": "Daughter",
    "Answer": "Grandmother"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 53,
    "Question": "A is the brother of B. B is the son of C. D is the father of A. How is C related to D?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Sister",
    "Option3": "Wife",
    "Option4": "Mother",
    "Answer": "Wife"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 54,
    "Question": "Introducing a boy, a girl said, 'He is the son of my father's only sister.' How is the boy related to the girl?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Cousin",
    "Option3": "Uncle",
    "Option4": "Nephew",
    "Answer": "Cousin"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 55,
    "Question": "If P is the brother of Q, Q is the sister of R, R is the father of S, and S is the daughter of T, then how is T related to P?",
    "Option1": "Sister",
    "Option2": "Sister-in-law",
    "Option3": "Wife",
    "Option4": "Mother",
    "Answer": "Sister-in-law"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 56,
    "Question": "Pointing to a photograph, a person says, 'I have no brother or sister but that man's father is my father's son.' Who is in the photograph?",
    "Option1": "His son",
    "Option2": "His father",
    "Option3": "His uncle",
    "Option4": "His nephew",
    "Answer": "His son"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 57,
    "Question": "A is B's daughter. B is C's mother. D is C's brother. How is D related to A?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Sister",
    "Option3": "Cousin",
    "Option4": "Son",
    "Answer": "Brother"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 58,
    "Question": "If 'A # B' means 'A is the father of B', 'A @ B' means 'A is the daughter of B', 'A * B' means 'A is the son of B', then how is P related to R in 'P # Q * R'?",
    "Option1": "Grandfather",
    "Option2": "Father",
    "Option3": "Uncle",
    "Option4": "Son",
    "Answer": "Grandfather"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 59,
    "Question": "Pointing to a woman, Rohit said, 'She is the daughter of the only child of my grandmother.' How is the woman related to Rohit?",
    "Option1": "Mother",
    "Option2": "Sister",
    "Option3": "Aunt",
    "Option4": "Cousin",
    "Answer": "Sister"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 60,
    "Question": "A is the mother of B. B is the husband of C. D is the daughter of C. How is A related to D?",
    "Option1": "Mother",
    "Option2": "Grandmother",
    "Option3": "Aunt",
    "Option4": "Mother-in-law",
    "Answer": "Grandmother"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 61,
    "Question": "Introducing a man, a woman said, 'His mother's husband is my only brother.' How is the man related to the woman?",
    "Option1": "Nephew",
    "Option2": "Brother",
    "Option3": "Son",
    "Option4": "Cousin",
    "Answer": "Nephew"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 62,
    "Question": "If 'X + Y' means 'X is the sister of Y', 'X - Y' means 'X is the mother of Y', 'X * Y' means 'X is the son of Y', then how is A related to C in 'A - B + C'?",
    "Option1": "Mother",
    "Option2": "Grandmother",
    "Option3": "Aunt",
    "Option4": "Daughter",
    "Answer": "Mother"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 63,
    "Question": "A and B are sisters. C is A's mother. D is C's father. E is D's mother. How is A related to E?",
    "Option1": "Granddaughter",
    "Option2": "Great Granddaughter",
    "Option3": "Daughter",
    "Option4": "Niece",
    "Answer": "Great Granddaughter"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 64,
    "Question": "Pointing to a man, a woman said, 'His wife's father is my husband's father.' How is the man related to the woman?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Brother-in-law",
    "Option3": "Son-in-law",
    "Option4": "Father-in-law",
    "Answer": "Brother-in-law"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 65,
    "Question": "If P is the father of Q, Q is the brother of R, and R is the daughter of S, then how is S related to P?",
    "Option1": "Wife",
    "Option2": "Mother",
    "Option3": "Sister",
    "Option4": "Daughter",
    "Answer": "Wife"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 66,
    "Question": "A is the son of B. B's sister C has a son D and a daughter E. F is the maternal uncle of D. How is A related to D?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Uncle",
    "Option3": "Cousin",
    "Option4": "Nephew",
    "Answer": "Cousin"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 67,
    "Question": "Introducing a woman, a man said, 'Her mother is the only daughter of my father-in-law.' How is the woman related to the man?",
    "Option1": "Wife",
    "Option2": "Mother",
    "Option3": "Sister",
    "Option4": "Daughter",
    "Answer": "Wife"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 68,
    "Question": "If 'A + B' means 'A is the mother of B', 'A - B' means 'A is the husband of B', 'A x B' means 'A is the son of B', then how is P related to T in 'P - Q x R + T'?",
    "Option1": "Father-in-law",
    "Option2": "Grandfather",
    "Option3": "Uncle",
    "Option4": "Husband",
    "Answer": "Father-in-law"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 69,
    "Question": "Pointing to a man in a photo, Rekha said, 'He is the only son of my father's mother.' How is Rekha related to the man?",
    "Option1": "Sister",
    "Option2": "Daughter",
    "Option3": "Niece",
    "Option4": "Aunt",
    "Answer": "Niece"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 70,
    "Question": "A is the brother of B. C is the father of A. D is the brother of E. E is the daughter of B. How is C related to D?",
    "Option1": "Father",
    "Option2": "Grandfather",
    "Option3": "Uncle",
    "Option4": "Brother-in-law",
    "Answer": "Grandfather"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 71,
    "Question": "If 'P is the father of Q', 'Q is the sister of R', 'R is the brother of S', then how is P related to S?",
    "Option1": "Father",
    "Option2": "Uncle",
    "Option3": "Brother",
    "Option4": "Grandfather",
    "Answer": "Father"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 72,
    "Question": "Introducing a girl, a man said, 'She is the daughter of my father's only daughter.' How is the girl related to the man?",
    "Option1": "Daughter",
    "Option2": "Niece",
    "Option3": "Sister",
    "Option4": "Cousin",
    "Answer": "Niece"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 73,
    "Question": "A is the son of B. B is the father of C. D is the mother of C. E is the brother of B. How is E related to D?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Uncle",
    "Option3": "Brother-in-law",
    "Option4": "Husband",
    "Answer": "Brother-in-law"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 74,
    "Question": "If 'M x N' means 'M is the father of N', 'M + N' means 'M is the daughter of N', 'M - N' means 'M is the sister of N', then how is A related to C in 'A x B + C'?",
    "Option1": "Grandfather",
    "Option2": "Uncle",
    "Option3": "Father",
    "Option4": "Son",
    "Answer": "Grandfather"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 75,
    "Question": "Pointing to a lady in the photograph, a girl said, 'She is the mother of my maternal grandfather's only son.' How is the lady related to the girl?",
    "Option1": "Mother",
    "Option2": "Aunt",
    "Option3": "Grandmother",
    "Option4": "Mother-in-law",
    "Answer": "Mother"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 76,
    "Question": "A is B's sister. C is B's mother. D is C's brother. E is D's mother. How is E related to A?",
    "Option1": "Grandmother",
    "Option2": "Great Grandmother",
    "Option3": "Aunt",
    "Option4": "Mother",
    "Answer": "Grandmother"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 77,
    "Question": "Introducing a woman, a man said, 'She is the daughter of the father of my uncle.' How is the woman related to the man?",
    "Option1": "Sister",
    "Option2": "Cousin",
    "Option3": "Aunt",
    "Option4": "Mother",
    "Answer": "Aunt"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 78,
    "Question": "If 'P @ Q' means 'P is the wife of Q', 'P # Q' means 'P is the son of Q', 'P * Q' means 'P is the brother of Q', then how is M related to R in 'M @ N * O # R'?",
    "Option1": "Mother-in-law",
    "Option2": "Grandmother",
    "Option3": "Wife",
    "Option4": "Daughter-in-law",
    "Answer": "Mother-in-law"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 79,
    "Question": "A is the mother of B. B is the son of C. D is the brother of C. E is the daughter of A. How is E related to D?",
    "Option1": "Sister",
    "Option2": "Cousin",
    "Option3": "Niece",
    "Option4": "Aunt",
    "Answer": "Niece"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 80,
    "Question": "Pointing to a man, a woman said, 'His wife is the only daughter of my father's mother.' How is the man related to the woman?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Husband",
    "Option3": "Uncle",
    "Option4": "Brother-in-law",
    "Answer": "Husband"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 81,
    "Question": "If 'P is the husband of Q', 'R is the son of P', 'S is the daughter of Q', then how is S related to R?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Sister",
    "Option3": "Cousin",
    "Option4": "Wife",
    "Answer": "Sister"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 82,
    "Question": "A is the sister of B. C is B's father. D is C's mother. E is D's son. How is E related to A?",
    "Option1": "Uncle",
    "Option2": "Brother",
    "Option3": "Father",
    "Option4": "Grandfather",
    "Answer": "Uncle"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 83,
    "Question": "Introducing a woman, a man said, 'She is the daughter of my mother's only son.' How is the woman related to the man?",
    "Option1": "Daughter",
    "Option2": "Niece",
    "Option3": "Sister",
    "Option4": "Mother",
    "Answer": "Daughter"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 84,
    "Question": "If 'A + B' means 'A is the father of B', 'A - B' means 'A is the wife of B', 'A x B' means 'A is the brother of B', how is P related to S in 'P x Q - R + S'?",
    "Option1": "Uncle",
    "Option2": "Father",
    "Option3": "Brother-in-law",
    "Option4": "Grandfather",
    "Answer": "Uncle"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 85,
    "Question": "Pointing to a boy, a girl said, 'His father is the only son of my grandfather.' How is the boy related to the girl?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Cousin",
    "Option3": "Son",
    "Option4": "Nephew",
    "Answer": "Brother"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 86,
    "Question": "A is the husband of B. C is the brother of A. D is the mother of C. E is the son of B. How is D related to E?",
    "Option1": "Mother",
    "Option2": "Grandmother",
    "Option3": "Aunt",
    "Option4": "Mother-in-law",
    "Answer": "Grandmother"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 87,
    "Question": "If 'X is the sister of Y', 'Y is the mother of Z', 'Z is the brother of W', then how is X related to W?",
    "Option1": "Mother",
    "Option2": "Aunt",
    "Option3": "Sister",
    "Option4": "Grandmother",
    "Answer": "Aunt"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 88,
    "Question": "Introducing a man, a woman said, 'His only brother is the father of my daughter's father.' How is the man related to the woman?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Uncle",
    "Option3": "Father",
    "Option4": "Husband",
    "Answer": "Uncle"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 89,
    "Question": "If 'M # N' means 'M is the father of N', 'M @ N' means 'M is the daughter of N', 'M * N' means 'M is the son of N', then how is P related to R in 'P * Q @ R'?",
    "Option1": "Grandson",
    "Option2": "Son",
    "Option3": "Nephew",
    "Option4": "Grandfather",
    "Answer": "Grandson"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 90,
    "Question": "A is the son of B. B is the mother of C. C is the daughter of D. How is D related to A?",
    "Option1": "Father",
    "Option2": "Mother",
    "Option3": "Uncle",
    "Option4": "Aunt",
    "Answer": "Father"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 91,
    "Question": "Pointing to a photo of a man, Pooja said, 'He is the son of the only daughter of my paternal grandfather.' How is the man related to Pooja?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Cousin",
    "Option3": "Uncle",
    "Option4": "Nephew",
    "Answer": "Brother"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 92,
    "Question": "If 'A + B' means 'A is the mother of B', 'A - B' means 'A is the brother of B', 'A x B' means 'A is the daughter of B', then how is P related to R in 'P x Q - R'?",
    "Option1": "Daughter",
    "Option2": "Niece",
    "Option3": "Aunt",
    "Option4": "Granddaughter",
    "Answer": "Daughter"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 93,
    "Question": "A and B are brothers. C is their mother. D is C's father. E is D's mother. How is A related to E?",
    "Option1": "Son",
    "Option2": "Grandson",
    "Option3": "Great Grandson",
    "Option4": "Nephew",
    "Answer": "Great Grandson"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 94,
    "Question": "Introducing a woman, a man said, 'Her son's father is the husband of my sister.' How is the woman related to the man?",
    "Option1": "Mother",
    "Option2": "Sister",
    "Option3": "Sister-in-law",
    "Option4": "Wife",
    "Answer": "Sister-in-law"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 95,
    "Question": "If 'P is the brother of Q', 'Q is the daughter of R', 'R is the husband of S', then how is S related to P?",
    "Option1": "Mother",
    "Option2": "Aunt",
    "Option3": "Sister",
    "Option4": "Wife",
    "Answer": "Mother"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 96,
    "Question": "A is the daughter of B. B is the son of C. D is the mother of C. E is the brother of A. How is D related to E?",
    "Option1": "Grandmother",
    "Option2": "Mother",
    "Option3": "Aunt",
    "Option4": "Great Aunt",
    "Answer": "Grandmother"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 97,
    "Question": "Pointing to a man, a woman said, 'His son is my only daughter's uncle.' How is the man related to the woman?",
    "Option1": "Father",
    "Option2": "Brother",
    "Option3": "Husband",
    "Option4": "Uncle",
    "Answer": "Father"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 98,
    "Question": "If 'M @ N' means 'M is the husband of N', 'M # N' means 'M is the daughter of N', 'M % N' means 'M is the father of N', then how is P related to R in 'P % Q # R'?",
    "Option1": "Father",
    "Option2": "Uncle",
    "Option3": "Grandfather",
    "Option4": "Son-in-law",
    "Answer": "Father"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 99,
    "Question": "A is the brother of B. C is the sister of A. D is the mother of C. E is the father of D. How is B related to E?",
    "Option1": "Grandson",
    "Option2": "Granddaughter",
    "Option3": "Grandson or Granddaughter",
    "Option4": "Son",
    "Answer": "Grandson or Granddaughter"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 100,
    "Question": "Introducing a girl, a boy said, 'She is the wife of my father-in-law's only son.' How is the girl related to the boy?",
    "Option1": "Sister",
    "Option2": "Wife",
    "Option3": "Daughter",
    "Option4": "Mother",
    "Answer": "Wife"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 101,
    "Question": "If 'A + B' means 'A is the father of B', 'A - B' means 'A is the wife of B', 'A x B' means 'A is the brother of B', and 'A / B' means 'A is the daughter of B', then how is P related to T in the expression 'P / Q + R - T'?",
    "Option1": "Daughter",
    "Option2": "Granddaughter",
    "Option3": "Niece",
    "Option4": "Aunt",
    "Answer": "Granddaughter"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 102,
    "Question": "Pointing to a photograph, a man says, 'The man in the photo is the son of my father's only daughter-in-law.' How is the man in the photo related to the speaker?",
    "Option1": "Son",
    "Option2": "Grandson",
    "Option3": "Nephew",
    "Option4": "Brother",
    "Answer": "Son"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 103,
    "Question": "A is the son of B. C is the mother of A. D is the sister of C. How is D related to B?",
    "Option1": "Sister",
    "Option2": "Aunt",
    "Option3": "Sister-in-law",
    "Option4": "Mother-in-law",
    "Answer": "Sister-in-law"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 104,
    "Question": "If 'P is the son of Q', 'Q is the brother of R', 'R is the mother of S', then how is P related to S?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Cousin",
    "Option3": "Nephew",
    "Option4": "Uncle",
    "Answer": "Cousin"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 105,
    "Question": "Introducing a woman, a man said, 'Her brother's father is my grandfather's only son.' How is the woman related to the man?",
    "Option1": "Mother",
    "Option2": "Sister",
    "Option3": "Aunt",
    "Option4": "Cousin",
    "Answer": "Sister"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 106,
    "Question": "A is B's sister. C is B's mother. D is C's brother. E is D's father. Then how is A related to E?",
    "Option1": "Granddaughter",
    "Option2": "Great-granddaughter",
    "Option3": "Niece",
    "Option4": "Daughter",
    "Answer": "Great-granddaughter"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 107,
    "Question": "If 'M x N' means 'M is the mother of N', 'M + N' means 'M is the son of N', 'M - N' means 'M is the husband of N', then how is A related to C in 'A + B - C'?",
    "Option1": "Son",
    "Option2": "Grandson",
    "Option3": "Nephew",
    "Option4": "Father",
    "Answer": "Grandson"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 108,
    "Question": "Pointing to a man, a woman said, 'His only brother is the husband of my daughter's mother.' How is the man related to the woman?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Uncle",
    "Option3": "Brother-in-law",
    "Option4": "Husband",
    "Answer": "Brother-in-law"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 109,
    "Question": "A is the husband of B. C is the father of B. D is the son of A. How is C related to D?",
    "Option1": "Grandfather",
    "Option2": "Father",
    "Option3": "Uncle",
    "Option4": "Father-in-law",
    "Answer": "Grandfather"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 110,
    "Question": "If P is the brother of Q, and R is the father of P, and S is the mother of R, how is S related to Q?",
    "Option1": "Mother",
    "Option2": "Grandmother",
    "Option3": "Aunt",
    "Option4": "Sister",
    "Answer": "Grandmother"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 111,
    "Question": "Introducing a boy, a girl said, 'He is the only son of the wife of my father's brother.' How is the boy related to the girl?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Cousin",
    "Option3": "Nephew",
    "Option4": "Uncle",
    "Answer": "Cousin"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 112,
    "Question": "A is the daughter of B. B is the mother of C. D is the brother of C. E is the son of D. How is B related to E?",
    "Option1": "Mother",
    "Option2": "Grandmother",
    "Option3": "Aunt",
    "Option4": "Mother-in-law",
    "Answer": "Grandmother"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 113,
    "Question": "If 'X @ Y' means 'X is the daughter of Y', 'X # Y' means 'X is the husband of Y', 'X * Y' means 'X is the brother of Y', then what does 'P # Q * R @ S' imply about P's relation to S?",
    "Option1": "Father-in-law",
    "Option2": "Son-in-law",
    "Option3": "Brother-in-law",
    "Option4": "Husband",
    "Answer": "Son-in-law"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 114,
    "Question": "Pointing to a man in a photograph, a woman says, 'His mother is the only daughter of my father's mother.' How is the man related to the woman?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Cousin",
    "Option3": "Son",
    "Option4": "Nephew",
    "Answer": "Cousin"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 115,
    "Question": "A is the brother of B. B is the sister of C. D is the mother of A. How is D related to C?",
    "Option1": "Mother",
    "Option2": "Sister",
    "Option3": "Aunt",
    "Option4": "Daughter",
    "Answer": "Mother"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 116,
    "Question": "Introducing a woman, a man said, 'Her only brother's son is my wife's brother.' How is the woman related to the man?",
    "Option1": "Mother",
    "Option2": "Aunt",
    "Option3": "Sister-in-law",
    "Option4": "Sister",
    "Answer": "Aunt"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 117,
    "Question": "If 'P is the mother of Q', 'Q is the son of R', 'R is the brother of S', then how is S related to P?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Sister",
    "Option3": "Brother-in-law",
    "Option4": "Cannot be determined",
    "Answer": "Brother-in-law"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 118,
    "Question": "A is B's father. C is B's wife. D is A's son. How is D related to C?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Brother-in-law",
    "Option3": "Father-in-law",
    "Option4": "Uncle",
    "Answer": "Brother-in-law"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 119,
    "Question": "Pointing to a girl, a man said, 'She is the daughter of my only sister's father.' How is the girl related to the man?",
    "Option1": "Daughter",
    "Option2": "Sister",
    "Option3": "Niece",
    "Option4": "Cousin",
    "Answer": "Daughter"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 120,
    "Question": "If 'A + B' means 'A is the son of B', 'A - B' means 'A is the daughter of B', 'A x B' means 'A is the wife of B', then how is P related to R in 'P x Q - R'?",
    "Option1": "Daughter-in-law",
    "Option2": "Son",
    "Option3": "Father",
    "Option4": "Husband",
    "Answer": "Husband"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 121,
    "Question": "A and B are brothers. C is the mother of A. D is the wife of B. How is D related to C?",
    "Option1": "Daughter",
    "Option2": "Daughter-in-law",
    "Option3": "Sister",
    "Option4": "Mother-in-law",
    "Answer": "Daughter-in-law"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 122,
    "Question": "Introducing a man, a woman said, 'His son is my son's uncle.' How is the man related to the woman?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Father",
    "Option3": "Husband",
    "Option4": "Uncle",
    "Answer": "Father"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 123,
    "Question": "If 'M & N' means 'M is the father of N', 'M % N' means 'M is the daughter of N', 'M $ N' means 'M is the wife of N', then how is P related to R in 'P % Q & R'?",
    "Option1": "Granddaughter",
    "Option2": "Daughter",
    "Option3": "Mother",
    "Option4": "Niece",
    "Answer": "Granddaughter"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 124,
    "Question": "Pointing to a lady, a man said, 'She is the mother of my mother's only grandson.' How is the lady related to the man?",
    "Option1": "Mother",
    "Option2": "Wife",
    "Option3": "Sister",
    "Option4": "Daughter-in-law",
    "Answer": "Wife"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 125,
    "Question": "A is the father of B. C is the son of A. D is the brother of C. How is D related to B?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Sister",
    "Option3": "Brother or Sister",
    "Option4": "Uncle",
    "Answer": "Brother or Sister"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 126,
    "Question": "If P is the mother of Q, and R is the sister of Q, and S is the daughter of R, how is P related to S?",
    "Option1": "Mother",
    "Option2": "Grandmother",
    "Option3": "Aunt",
    "Option4": "Mother-in-law",
    "Answer": "Grandmother"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 127,
    "Question": "Introducing a woman, a man said, 'Her husband is the only son of my mother-in-law.' How is the woman related to the man?",
    "Option1": "Mother",
    "Option2": "Wife",
    "Option3": "Sister",
    "Option4": "Daughter-in-law",
    "Answer": "Wife"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 128,
    "Question": "If 'X @ Y' means 'X is the son of Y', 'X # Y' means 'X is the wife of Y', 'X * Y' means 'X is the sister of Y', then what does 'P * Q # R @ S' imply about P's relation to S?",
    "Option1": "Niece",
    "Option2": "Daughter",
    "Option3": "Granddaughter",
    "Option4": "Aunt",
    "Answer": "Niece"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 129,
    "Question": "A is the husband of B. C is the brother of B. D is the son of A. How is C related to D?",
    "Option1": "Father",
    "Option2": "Uncle",
    "Option3": "Brother-in-law",
    "Option4": "Nephew",
    "Answer": "Uncle"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 130,
    "Question": "Pointing to a man in a photograph, a woman says, 'He is the only son of the wife of my mother's brother.' How is the man related to the woman?",
    "Option1": "Cousin",
    "Option2": "Brother",
    "Option3": "Nephew",
    "Option4": "Son",
    "Answer": "Cousin"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 131,
    "Question": "If 'A + B' means 'A is the daughter of B', 'A - B' means 'A is the husband of B', 'A x B' means 'A is the brother of B', then how is P related to R in 'P - Q x R'?",
    "Option1": "Father",
    "Option2": "Brother-in-law",
    "Option3": "Husband",
    "Option4": "Son-in-law",
    "Answer": "Husband"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 132,
    "Question": "A and B are brothers. C is their father. D is E's mother. E is A's son. How is B related to D?",
    "Option1": "Father",
    "Option2": "Uncle",
    "Option3": "Brother",
    "Option4": "Husband",
    "Answer": "Husband"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 133,
    "Question": "Introducing a girl, a boy said, 'Her mother is the only daughter of my maternal grandmother.' How is the girl related to the boy?",
    "Option1": "Sister",
    "Option2": "Cousin",
    "Option3": "Aunt",
    "Option4": "Mother",
    "Answer": "Cousin"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 134,
    "Question": "If 'P is the brother of Q', 'Q is the daughter of R', 'R is the father of S', then how is P related to S?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Cousin",
    "Option3": "Uncle",
    "Option4": "Father",
    "Answer": "Brother"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 135,
    "Question": "A is the mother of B. C is the son of A. D is the brother of B. How is D related to C?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Sister",
    "Option3": "Brother or Sister",
    "Option4": "Nephew",
    "Answer": "Brother or Sister"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 136,
    "Question": "Pointing to a man, a woman said, 'His son is my son's father.' How is the man related to the woman?",
    "Option1": "Father",
    "Option2": "Husband",
    "Option3": "Brother",
    "Option4": "Uncle",
    "Answer": "Husband"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 137,
    "Question": "If 'M @ N' means 'M is the father of N', 'M # N' means 'M is the sister of N', 'M % N' means 'M is the son of N', then how is P related to R in 'P # Q @ R'?",
    "Option1": "Sister",
    "Option2": "Aunt",
    "Option3": "Daughter",
    "Option4": "Mother",
    "Answer": "Daughter"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 138,
    "Question": "A is the son of B. B is the father of C. C is the sister of D. How is A related to D?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Sister",
    "Option3": "Brother or Sister",
    "Option4": "Uncle",
    "Answer": "Brother"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 139,
    "Question": "Introducing a woman, a man said, 'She is the daughter of the only son of my grandmother.' How is the woman related to the man?",
    "Option1": "Mother",
    "Option2": "Sister",
    "Option3": "Aunt",
    "Option4": "Daughter",
    "Answer": "Sister"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 140,
    "Question": "If 'X + Y' means 'X is the mother of Y', 'X - Y' means 'X is the brother of Y', 'X * Y' means 'X is the father of Y', then how is A related to D in 'A + B * D'?",
    "Option1": "Grandmother",
    "Option2": "Mother",
    "Option3": "Aunt",
    "Option4": "Daughter",
    "Answer": "Grandmother"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 141,
    "Question": "A is the father of B. C is the mother of B. D is the sister of A. How is D related to C?",
    "Option1": "Sister",
    "Option2": "Sister-in-law",
    "Option3": "Aunt",
    "Option4": "Mother-in-law",
    "Answer": "Sister-in-law"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 142,
    "Question": "Pointing to a man, a woman said, 'He is the son of my only sister's mother-in-law.' How is the man related to the woman?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Brother-in-law",
    "Option3": "Nephew",
    "Option4": "Uncle",
    "Answer": "Brother-in-law"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 143,
    "Question": "If 'P is the husband of Q', 'R is the father of P', 'S is the mother of Q', how is R related to S?",
    "Option1": "Father-in-law",
    "Option2": "Mother-in-law",
    "Option3": "Husband",
    "Option4": "Brother",
    "Answer": "Husband"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 144,
    "Question": "A is B's daughter. B is C's husband. D is A's sister. E is C's brother. How is E related to D?",
    "Option1": "Uncle",
    "Option2": "Brother-in-law",
    "Option3": "Father",
    "Option4": "Cousin",
    "Answer": "Uncle"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 145,
    "Question": "Introducing a boy, a girl said, 'His father's only daughter is my mother.' How is the boy related to the girl?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Cousin",
    "Option3": "Uncle",
    "Option4": "Nephew",
    "Answer": "Brother"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 146,
    "Question": "If 'M @ N' means 'M is the husband of N', 'M # N' means 'M is the daughter of N', 'M % N' means 'M is the brother of N', then how is P related to R in 'P % Q # R'?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Uncle",
    "Option3": "Son",
    "Option4": "Nephew",
    "Answer": "Uncle"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 147,
    "Question": "A is the son of P. Q is the daughter of A. R is the mother of Q. S is the brother of R. How is S related to P?",
    "Option1": "Son-in-law",
    "Option2": "Brother-in-law",
    "Option3": "Nephew",
    "Option4": "Uncle",
    "Answer": "Son-in-law"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 148,
    "Question": "Pointing to a woman, a man said, 'She is the sister of my mother's husband.' How is the woman related to the man?",
    "Option1": "Mother",
    "Option2": "Aunt",
    "Option3": "Sister",
    "Option4": "Mother-in-law",
    "Answer": "Aunt"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 149,
    "Question": "If 'P is the mother of Q', 'Q is the son of R', 'R is the sister of S', how is P related to S?",
    "Option1": "Mother",
    "Option2": "Aunt",
    "Option3": "Sister-in-law",
    "Option4": "Mother-in-law",
    "Answer": "Mother-in-law"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 150,
    "Question": "A is B's father. C is B's sister. D is C's mother. E is D's son. How is E related to A?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Brother-in-law",
    "Option3": "Uncle",
    "Option4": "Nephew",
    "Answer": "Brother"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 151,
    "Question": "Introducing a man, a woman said, 'His daughter is my sister's mother.' How is the man related to the woman?",
    "Option1": "Father",
    "Option2": "Uncle",
    "Option3": "Brother",
    "Option4": "Husband",
    "Answer": "Father"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 152,
    "Question": "If 'A + B' means 'A is the daughter of B', 'A - B' means 'A is the husband of B', 'A x B' means 'A is the brother of B', then how is P related to S in 'P x Q - R + S'?",
    "Option1": "Brother-in-law",
    "Option2": "Uncle",
    "Option3": "Father",
    "Option4": "Grandfather",
    "Answer": "Uncle"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 153,
    "Question": "Pointing to a photo of a girl, Suresh said, 'She is the only daughter of my paternal grandfather's only son.' How is Suresh related to the girl?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Cousin",
    "Option3": "Uncle",
    "Option4": "Son",
    "Answer": "Brother"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 154,
    "Question": "A is the son of B. C is the sister of A. D is the mother of C. How is D related to B?",
    "Option1": "Mother",
    "Option2": "Sister",
    "Option3": "Wife",
    "Option4": "Aunt",
    "Answer": "Wife"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 155,
    "Question": "If 'X is the brother of Y', 'Y is the son of Z', 'Z is the husband of W', then how is W related to X?",
    "Option1": "Mother",
    "Option2": "Aunt",
    "Option3": "Sister",
    "Option4": "Mother-in-law",
    "Answer": "Mother"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 156,
    "Question": "Introducing a woman, a man said, 'Her mother's daughter is my only sister.' How is the woman related to the man?",
    "Option1": "Sister",
    "Option2": "Mother",
    "Option3": "Aunt",
    "Option4": "Wife",
    "Answer": "Sister"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 157,
    "Question": "If 'M x N' means 'M is the father of N', 'M + N' means 'M is the daughter of N', 'M - N' means 'M is the sister of N', then how is A related to C in 'A + B - C'?",
    "Option1": "Daughter",
    "Option2": "Niece",
    "Option3": "Aunt",
    "Option4": "Mother",
    "Answer": "Niece"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 158,
    "Question": "A is the husband of B. C is the daughter of B. D is the son of A. How is D related to C?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Sister",
    "Option3": "Cousin",
    "Option4": "Nephew",
    "Answer": "Brother"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 159,
    "Question": "Pointing to a man, a woman said, 'His mother's daughter is the wife of my only son.' How is the man related to the woman?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Son-in-law",
    "Option3": "Father-in-law",
    "Option4": "Brother-in-law",
    "Answer": "Brother-in-law"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 160,
    "Question": "If 'P is the mother of Q', 'Q is the sister of R', 'R is the brother of S', then how is P related to S?",
    "Option1": "Mother",
    "Option2": "Aunt",
    "Option3": "Grandmother",
    "Option4": "Mother-in-law",
    "Answer": "Mother"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 161,
    "Question": "A is the daughter of B. B is the father of C. D is the mother of C. E is the brother of D. How is A related to E?",
    "Option1": "Niece",
    "Option2": "Daughter",
    "Option3": "Cousin",
    "Option4": "Sister",
    "Answer": "Niece"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 162,
    "Question": "Introducing a woman, a man said, 'Her husband is my father's only son.' How is the woman related to the man?",
    "Option1": "Mother",
    "Option2": "Sister",
    "Option3": "Wife",
    "Option4": "Daughter",
    "Answer": "Wife"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 163,
    "Question": "If 'X @ Y' means 'X is the father of Y', 'X # Y' means 'X is the daughter of Y', 'X * Y' means 'X is the son of Y', then how is P related to R in 'P * Q # R'?",
    "Option1": "Grandson",
    "Option2": "Son",
    "Option3": "Nephew",
    "Option4": "Grandfather",
    "Answer": "Grandson"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 164,
    "Question": "A and B are married. C and D are siblings. C is A's sister. How is D related to B?",
    "Option1": "Brother-in-law",
    "Option2": "Sister-in-law",
    "Option3": "Brother or Sister-in-law",
    "Option4": "Nephew",
    "Answer": "Brother or Sister-in-law"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 165,
    "Question": "Pointing to a girl, a man said, 'She is the granddaughter of my mother's only son.' How is the girl related to the man?",
    "Option1": "Daughter",
    "Option2": "Niece",
    "Option3": "Sister",
    "Option4": "Cousin",
    "Answer": "Daughter"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 166,
    "Question": "If 'P is the father of Q', 'Q is the brother of R', 'R is the son of S', then how is S related to P?",
    "Option1": "Mother",
    "Option2": "Wife",
    "Option3": "Sister",
    "Option4": "Mother-in-law",
    "Answer": "Wife"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 167,
    "Question": "A is the mother of B. C is the husband of B. D is the son of C. How is A related to D?",
    "Option1": "Mother",
    "Option2": "Grandmother",
    "Option3": "Aunt",
    "Option4": "Mother-in-law",
    "Answer": "Grandmother"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 168,
    "Question": "Introducing a woman, a man said, 'Her husband's brother is my father.' How is the woman related to the man?",
    "Option1": "Mother",
    "Option2": "Aunt",
    "Option3": "Sister-in-law",
    "Option4": "Mother-in-law",
    "Answer": "Mother"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 169,
    "Question": "If 'M & N' means 'M is the brother of N', 'M % N' means 'M is the father of N', 'M $ N' means 'M is the wife of N', then how is P related to R in 'P $ Q % R'?",
    "Option1": "Mother-in-law",
    "Option2": "Mother",
    "Option3": "Wife",
    "Option4": "Daughter",
    "Answer": "Mother"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 170,
    "Question": "A is the daughter of B. B is the brother of C. D is the mother of C. How is A related to D?",
    "Option1": "Granddaughter",
    "Option2": "Niece",
    "Option3": "Daughter",
    "Option4": "Aunt",
    "Answer": "Niece"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 171,
    "Question": "Pointing to a man in a photograph, a woman says, 'He is the only son of the wife of my only brother.' How is the man related to the woman?",
    "Option1": "Nephew",
    "Option2": "Son",
    "Option3": "Cousin",
    "Option4": "Brother",
    "Answer": "Nephew"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 172,
    "Question": "If 'A + B' means 'A is the mother of B', 'A - B' means 'A is the husband of B', 'A x B' means 'A is the son of B', then how is P related to T in 'P x Q - R + T'?",
    "Option1": "Grandson",
    "Option2": "Son",
    "Option3": "Nephew",
    "Option4": "Grandfather",
    "Answer": "Grandson"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 173,
    "Question": "A is the brother of B. C is the daughter of A. D is the wife of C. How is B related to D?",
    "Option1": "Brother-in-law",
    "Option2": "Uncle",
    "Option3": "Father-in-law",
    "Option4": "Son-in-law",
    "Answer": "Uncle"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 174,
    "Question": "Introducing a girl, a boy said, 'She is the sister of my mother's only son.' How is the girl related to the boy?",
    "Option1": "Sister",
    "Option2": "Cousin",
    "Option3": "Aunt",
    "Option4": "Mother",
    "Answer": "Sister"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 175,
    "Question": "If 'P is the son of Q', 'Q is the father of R', 'R is the sister of S', then how is P related to S?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Sister",
    "Option3": "Brother or Sister",
    "Option4": "Nephew",
    "Answer": "Brother"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 176,
    "Question": "A is B's mother. C is A's son. D is B's daughter. E is C's brother. How is D related to E?",
    "Option1": "Sister",
    "Option2": "Cousin",
    "Option3": "Niece",
    "Option4": "Daughter",
    "Answer": "Sister"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 177,
    "Question": "Pointing to a man, a woman said, 'His only son is my son's father.' How is the man related to the woman?",
    "Option1": "Father",
    "Option2": "Husband",
    "Option3": "Brother",
    "Option4": "Uncle",
    "Answer": "Husband"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 178,
    "Question": "If 'X @ Y' means 'X is the daughter of Y', 'X # Y' means 'X is the husband of Y', 'X * Y' means 'X is the brother of Y', then what does 'P # Q * R @ S' imply about P's relation to S?",
    "Option1": "Father-in-law",
    "Option2": "Son-in-law",
    "Option3": "Brother-in-law",
    "Option4": "Husband",
    "Answer": "Son-in-law"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 179,
    "Question": "A is the husband of B. C is the father of A. D is the daughter of B. How is C related to D?",
    "Option1": "Grandfather",
    "Option2": "Father",
    "Option3": "Uncle",
    "Option4": "Father-in-law",
    "Answer": "Grandfather"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 180,
    "Question": "Introducing a woman, a man said, 'Her mother's only daughter is my wife.' How is the woman related to the man?",
    "Option1": "Sister",
    "Option2": "Wife",
    "Option3": "Mother",
    "Option4": "Daughter",
    "Answer": "Wife"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 181,
    "Question": "If 'P is the brother of Q', 'Q is the mother of R', 'R is the son of S', then how is S related to P?",
    "Option1": "Brother-in-law",
    "Option2": "Uncle",
    "Option3": "Father",
    "Option4": "Cannot be determined",
    "Answer": "Father"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 182,
    "Question": "A is the daughter of B. C is the son of B. D is the sister of C. How is D related to A?",
    "Option1": "Sister",
    "Option2": "Brother",
    "Option3": "Cousin",
    "Option4": "Niece",
    "Answer": "Sister"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 183,
    "Question": "Pointing to a boy, a girl said, 'He is the son of the only brother of my mother.' How is the boy related to the girl?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Cousin",
    "Option3": "Nephew",
    "Option4": "Uncle",
    "Answer": "Cousin"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 184,
    "Question": "If 'M % N' means 'M is the father of N', 'M $ N' means 'M is the sister of N', 'M @ N' means 'M is the wife of N', then how is P related to R in 'P @ Q % R'?",
    "Option1": "Mother",
    "Option2": "Mother-in-law",
    "Option3": "Grandmother",
    "Option4": "Aunt",
    "Answer": "Mother"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 185,
    "Question": "A is the mother of B. B is the husband of C. D is the sister of A. How is D related to C?",
    "Option1": "Mother-in-law",
    "Option2": "Aunt",
    "Option3": "Sister-in-law",
    "Option4": "Mother",
    "Answer": "Aunt"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 186,
    "Question": "Introducing a man, a woman said, 'His mother's only daughter is my only sister.' How is the man related to the woman?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Cousin",
    "Option3": "Nephew",
    "Option4": "Son",
    "Answer": "Brother"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 187,
    "Question": "If 'P is the brother of Q', 'Q is the daughter of R', 'R is the husband of S', then how is S related to P?",
    "Option1": "Mother",
    "Option2": "Wife",
    "Option3": "Sister",
    "Option4": "Mother-in-law",
    "Answer": "Mother"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 188,
    "Question": "A is B's sister. C is B's brother. D is C's father. E is D's mother. How is A related to E?",
    "Option1": "Granddaughter",
    "Option2": "Great-granddaughter",
    "Option3": "Niece",
    "Option4": "Daughter",
    "Answer": "Great-granddaughter"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 189,
    "Question": "Pointing to a man, a woman said, 'His wife is the only daughter of my husband's mother.' How is the man related to the woman?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Husband",
    "Option3": "Brother-in-law",
    "Option4": "Father",
    "Answer": "Husband"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 190,
    "Question": "If 'A + B' means 'A is the son of B', 'A - B' means 'A is the daughter of B', 'A x B' means 'A is the wife of B', then how is P related to S in 'P x Q - R + S'?",
    "Option1": "Son",
    "Option2": "Grandson",
    "Option3": "Nephew",
    "Option4": "Father",
    "Answer": "Son"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 191,
    "Question": "A is the son of B. B is the mother of C. C is the sister of D. How is D related to A?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Sister",
    "Option3": "Brother or Sister",
    "Option4": "Cousin",
    "Answer": "Brother or Sister"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 192,
    "Question": "Introducing a woman, a man said, 'She is the mother of the only child of my father-in-law.' How is the woman related to the man?",
    "Option1": "Mother",
    "Option2": "Wife",
    "Option3": "Sister",
    "Option4": "Daughter-in-law",
    "Answer": "Wife"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 193,
    "Question": "If 'X is the sister of Y', 'Y is the son of Z', 'Z is the father of W', then how is X related to W?",
    "Option1": "Sister",
    "Option2": "Brother",
    "Option3": "Cousin",
    "Option4": "Aunt",
    "Answer": "Sister"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 194,
    "Question": "A is the daughter of B. C is the brother of B. D is the son of C. How is A related to D?",
    "Option1": "Sister",
    "Option2": "Cousin",
    "Option3": "Niece",
    "Option4": "Aunt",
    "Answer": "Cousin"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 195,
    "Question": "Pointing to a man, a woman said, 'His mother is the only daughter of my mother's father.' How is the man related to the woman?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Uncle",
    "Option3": "Nephew",
    "Option4": "Son",
    "Answer": "Nephew"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 196,
    "Question": "If 'M % N' means 'M is the father of N', 'M $ N' means 'M is the sister of N', 'M @ N' means 'M is the wife of N', then how is P related to R in 'P $ Q % R'?",
    "Option1": "Aunt",
    "Option2": "Niece",
    "Option3": "Daughter",
    "Option4": "Mother",
    "Answer": "Aunt"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 197,
    "Question": "A is the husband of B. C is the mother of A. D is the son of B. How is C related to D?",
    "Option1": "Mother",
    "Option2": "Grandmother",
    "Option3": "Aunt",
    "Option4": "Mother-in-law",
    "Answer": "Grandmother"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 198,
    "Question": "Introducing a girl, a man said, 'Her mother's husband is my father's only son.' How is the girl related to the man?",
    "Option1": "Daughter",
    "Option2": "Niece",
    "Option3": "Sister",
    "Option4": "Cousin",
    "Answer": "Daughter"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 199,
    "Question": "If 'P is the mother of Q', 'Q is the daughter of R', 'R is the brother of S', then how is S related to P?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Son",
    "Option3": "Brother-in-law",
    "Option4": "Husband",
    "Answer": "Brother-in-law"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 200,
    "Question": "A is the father of B. C is the wife of B. D is the mother of C. How is D related to A?",
    "Option1": "Mother",
    "Option2": "Mother-in-law",
    "Option3": "Sister-in-law",
    "Option4": "Aunt",
    "Answer": "Mother-in-law"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 201,
    "Question": "Pointing to a man, a woman said, 'His son is my son's brother.' How is the man related to the woman?",
    "Option1": "Father",
    "Option2": "Husband",
    "Option3": "Brother",
    "Option4": "Uncle",
    "Answer": "Husband"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 202,
    "Question": "If 'A + B' means 'A is the father of B', 'A - B' means 'A is the wife of B', 'A x B' means 'A is the brother of B', then how is P related to T in 'P - Q + R x T'?",
    "Option1": "Mother-in-law",
    "Option2": "Grandmother",
    "Option3": "Mother",
    "Option4": "Aunt",
    "Answer": "Mother"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 203,
    "Question": "A is the brother of B. C is the sister of D. A's son is D's brother. How is B related to C?",
    "Option1": "Father",
    "Option2": "Uncle",
    "Option3": "Brother",
    "Option4": "Nephew",
    "Answer": "Uncle"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 204,
    "Question": "Introducing a woman, a man said, 'She is the mother of my mother's only sister.' How is the woman related to the man?",
    "Option1": "Mother",
    "Option2": "Grandmother",
    "Option3": "Aunt",
    "Option4": "Mother-in-law",
    "Answer": "Grandmother"
  },
  {
    "question_no.": 205,
    "Question": "If 'P is the son of Q', 'Q is the mother of R', 'R is the brother of S', then how is P related to S?",
    "Option1": "Brother",
    "Option2": "Cousin",
    "Option3": "Nephew",
    "Option4": "Uncle",
    "Answer": "Cousin"
  }
]